這是Dorris Archer 愛達荷州博伊西 今年失蹤的第三個女人
This is dorris archer,she's the third woman to go missing in boise,idaho,this year,
之前是Paula Renmar和Samantha Rush
along with paula renmar and samantha rush.
他們的失蹤間隔約為2個月
They went missing roughly 2 months apart.
你好
Well,hello.
怎麼 你加入男孩樂隊了?
What,did you join a boy band?
沒
No.
好的 我們要關注什麼群體? 30歲上下的女性
Ok,so what are we looking at here? Late 20s,early 30s.
都還未婚 但有兩人戀愛中
All single,though two are in committed relationships.
都獨立生活
All living on their own.
都是很普通的郊區住房 不明嫌犯得以避人耳目
Looks like normal suburban houses. Gives the unsub privacy.
受害者的差異比相似點更引人注目
The differences are more striking than the similarities.
髮色不同 體形不同
Different hair colors, different body shapes.
他的作案手法我們瞭解嗎?
What do you know about his M.O.?
這也是我們被邀的原因
That's why we were invited in.
綁架現場非常乾淨
The abduction sites are pristine.
沒有除受害者之外的他人DNA
And there's no dna besides the victims',
而且也沒強行侵入和爭鬥的痕跡
and there's no sign of forced entry or a struggle.
直至被綁2到3天後 才有人報告她們失蹤
And the victims aren't reported missing until 2 or 3 days after they're abducted.
2 3天啊...
2 or 3 days...
這樣的女人突然杳無音信 一定會有人注意
Women like this don't just vanish without somebody noticing.
是的 因此我讓Garcia去挖掘她們的生活
Yes. Which is why I asked garcia to dig into their lives.
我大略看了看她們的網上活動
And when I took a look at their online activity,
馬上看出了不明嫌犯的犯案行徑
I could easily see how the unsub is doing it.
- 在線社交網站 - 對 比如Facebook Twitter
- Social networking sites. - Yeah. Facebook,twitter.
隨便說一個浪費時間的在線社交網站 受害者一定是註冊用戶
You name an online life-sharing time suck, the victims were on it.
看一眼她們最後發表的信息 說的東西幾乎一樣
And if you look at each of their last posts, they say kind of the same thing...
出城散心 出差 或者度假
Going out of town, going on a business trip, going on a vacation.
但如果看下三者的發表時間和日期
But when you look at the time and date stamp of each of these,
來點"陰陽魔界"的配樂吧
cue the "twilight zone" music,
因為 三條都是在受害者 失蹤之後的早晨發佈的
because they were all posted the morning after each of them went missing.
是不明嫌犯發佈的
The unsub posted them.
在線社交網絡 為嫌犯獵取目標提供了便利
Social networks are an easy way for an unsub to target his victims.
這些受害的女人的生活非常透明
These women were especially open.
她們發佈全部的生活細節 包括晚餐吃什麼 去哪堿鸕|等
They posted everything from what they were having for dinner to where they were going on dates.
不明嫌犯把受害者加為好友 以此為幌子來控制受害者
So this unsub friends his victims and then uses that as a cover once he takes them.
這表明他可以"黑"進她們的賬戶 所以他電腦水平出色
That means he can hack into their accounts. So he's excellent with computers.
可以肯定他很有耐心 很有組織性
Definitely profiles as patient and organized.
他不遺餘力地 抹掉現場所有的犯罪證據
He's obsessive enough to remove all forensic details,
而且為了誘拐目標不惜耐心等待2個月
but also patient enough to wait 2 months before abductions.
他真是百忍成金 有3天時間可以對這些女人隨意為所欲為
He can afford to be. He gets 3 days to do whatever he wants to these women.
我們得做好準備 這些女人可能已經死了
That means we need to assume these women are already dead.
現在的問題是 他對她們都做了什麼?
The question is what he does while he has them.
犯罪心理 第五季 第22集 網絡永恆
Criminal Minds Season05 Episode22 The Internet Is Forever
"溝通 其最顯著的問題在於 我們總幻想它確實發生過"
"the single biggest problem with communication is the illusion that it has taken place."
喬治·蕭伯納
George bernard shaw.
不明嫌犯使用社交網絡獵取受害者 我們能以網絡獵取他嗎?
So if this unsub is using social networks to find his victims,can't we use that to find him?
當然 假設這些女人 每人有100個在線好友
Yeah,if these women each had 100 friends following them,
那嫌犯會在好友名單的交集上 對嗎?
then the unsub would pop up on each of their lists, right?
John Fordham警探負責此事 他調查了所有人
Uh,the detective in charge, john fordham, he looked into their groups.
都被排除
Everyone checked out.
社交網站安全程度之低 讓人愕然
Social networking sites are surprisingly insecure.
Facebook最近試圖更新他們的隱私設置
Facebook recently tried to update all their privacy settings,
通過此舉 可把所有人的隱私文件 全部公開瀏覽
and in doing so, they made everybody's profiles viewable.
誰能解釋下 人們為何熱衷此類網站?
Can somebody explain to me the appeal of these sites?
"今晚我吃壽司 贊"
"eating sushi tonight. Yum."
"老大讓我加班 杯具"
"boss is keeping me late at work. Grr."
誰的生活會重要到 讓所有人都有興趣關注這些細節?
Whose life is so important that we'd be interested in this kind of detail?
我搞不懂 但一傳十十傳百嘛 沒有誰的生活那麼有趣
I don't know. I guess that's the running joke,right? I mean,nobody is.
但我們都寧願相信 的確有觀眾在關注我們的一舉一動
But we'd all like to believe there's actually an audience out there that wants to follow our every move.
某些網站還有內置的GPS功能
You know,some sites actually have a gps feature built in.
每當有人發表評論 就可以準確測出他的具體位置
You can tell exactly where someone is every time they post a new comment.
這可以解釋他獵取目標的方式 但無法解釋他是怎麼進入受害者住處
This is telling us how he's finding them, but it's not telling us how he's getting into their houses.
我敢肯定他配過她們的鑰匙
At the very least,I believe that he has copies of their keys.
Dorris Archer家裝有家庭安全系統
Dorris archer had a home security system installed,
但有人在凌晨1點56分輸入關閉口令 所以他也知道這點
but the disable code was entered at 1:56 a.M. So he knew that,too.
他還找到辦法搞定了她的狗
He also found a way to deal with her dog.
去年她從收容所收養了一隻德國牧羊犬 她失蹤那晚 狗也失蹤了
A german shepherd she adopted from the pound last year went missing the night that she did.
所以 這傢伙在受害者失蹤前 一定多次進出受害者的房子
All right,so this guy's gotta be in and out of the house well before the night of the disappearance.
他一定使了些手段 說服受害者讓他進屋
He comes up with some ruse, talks his way inside,
一旦足夠熟悉受害者的房間
then once he's familiar enough with the house,
他就會來綁架她們 毫無忌憚
he knows he can come back and kidnap them without disturbing anything.
哪些人進你的房間你會放鬆警惕?
What about the people who come into your house that you don't consider a threat?
房屋修理員 溜狗人
Home repair guys, dog-walkers.
對 Fordham警探也研究過這點
Yeah,detective fordham looked into that,too.
這些人根本都不是殺手型
No one even came close to being a killer.
好吧 Morgan和Prentiss 從最近的綁架現場著手
Ok,morgan and prentiss,start with the last abduction sites.
看能否發現他的作案手法
See if anything point to his M.O.
Dave 你和Reid以及JJ追溯受害者的生活
Dave,you,reid,and jj go back over the women's lives.
先從她們社交網絡的好友著手
Start with their friends on the social networking sites.
如果這是不明嫌犯獵取受害者的途徑
If this is how the unsub is finding them,
也許已有新的受害者上鉤 自己還沒意識到
maybe they're connected to him without even realizing it.
愛達荷州 博伊西
Fordham警探
Uh,detective fordham.
- Jareau探員? - 是的
- Agent jareau? - Yeah.
特別督察探員Hotcher Rossi Spencer Reid博士
- Uh,these are ssa hotcher,rossi, and Dr. Spencer reid. - How do you do?
謝謝你們前來 我們真的需要你們的幫助
Well,thank you for coming. We can really use your help.
有人願意跟我們談談受害者的情況嗎?
Did you find anyone willing to talk to us about the victims?
問題不是找誰談 而是不跟誰談
The problem wasn't who to bring in. It was who not to.
我們找的這個男人 可能通過社交網絡認識你的女兒
The man we're looking for might have found your daughter through her social networks.
- Paula提到過新認識什麼人嗎? - 沒
- Did paula mention anyone new in her life? - No.
有沒有現實中不認識 卻在網上關注她的好友?
No one who started following her as a friend, someone she didn't recognize?
我真不瞭解這些東西
I don't really know how those work.
有人給我發了電子郵件 慶賀Paula的晉陞
Someone sent me an email congratulating me on paula's promotion.
我還不知道她升職了呢
I didn't even know.
我就去問她 她說 "媽 我上周已經曝上網了"
And when I asked her, she said, "mom,I put that on my wall last week."
兩天後 她就失蹤了
She was gone 2 days later.
Samantha總是熱衷於更新她的狀態
Samantha was rigorous about keeping her status updated.
她沉迷於社交網站
She's obsessed with those sites.
那我想 她知道誰在關注她吧?
So I'm assuming she knew who followed her,then?
哦 天呢 不可能 她有一千多個好友
Oh,god,no. She had over 1,000 friends.
- 怎麼這麼多? - 我和她都是做房地產的
- Why so many? - We both worked in real estate.
她覺得這是個推銷自己的好辦法
She saw it as the perfect way to promote herself.
等等 那即使她告訴了所有人 自己的動態
So,wait. Even though she told all those people what she was doing,
她也不知道誰在關注自己?
she didn't know who was following her?
你有沒有覺得 自己郵件多得 都要淹死在堶惜F?
You ever have so much email, you feeling like you're drowning in it?
- 我沒有電子郵箱的 - 不是吧?
- Actually, I don't have email. - Seriously?
那我好好跟你解釋下
Then let me break it down for you.
這些網站就像抽了瘋的電子郵箱
These websites are like email on crack.
不可能和所有人都保持聯繫的
It's impossible to keep up with everybody.
有關你女友的失蹤 我們只有幾個問題
We just have a few more questions about your girlfriend's disappearance.
Dorris有沒有提過有人去她家?
Did dorris ever mention letting someone in her home?
比如說?
Like who?
我們在調查誰會知道 她家埵w保系統的密碼
Well,we're just trying to figure out who would know the code to her home security.
一定是某個她信任的人
It must have been someone she trusted with the combination.
不會的 她是個聰明人 總是做好預防措施
No. She was smart. She took precautions.
所以她才會養Bruno
That's the whole reason she got bruno.
Bruno... 那條狗 是看門狗?
Bruno... The dog. So he was a guard dog?
是的 她訓練了它六個星期
Yeah. She trained him for like 6 weeks.
好了
Ok.
我知道讓你看這個會很難受 但你看看有沒有不一樣的地方?
I know these are hard to look at, but do you see anything different?
罪犯可能動了什麼地方進入房子
Something he may have done to get himself inside.
- 這個不對啊 - 什麼?
- This isn't right. - What's that?
照片的位置 這是我們第一次約會
The photographs. This is when we first started dating.
右邊這張應該放在左邊的
The one on the right should be on the left.
好吧 會不會是她自己重新擺過了?
Ok. And she wouldn't have rearranged them herself?
不會的 她這麼放是有理由的
No. She arranged them a certain way to tell a story.
是告訴別人... 我們相愛的故事
It was... It was how we fell in love.
- 好的 JJ 我在搬了 - 看到了?
- Ok,jj,I got it. - You see it?
看到了 看起來他想把什麼東西 裝在牆上
Actually,yeah. Looks like he did try to hang something on the wall.
上面還有點殘留
There's even a little residue left over.
Morgan
Morgan.
- 回頭再打給你 - 好的
- Let me call you back. - Yeah.
- 怎麼 發現什麼了? - 嘿 這上面也有一個
- Yeah,what do you got? - Hey,I got one up here,too.
他想在那上面裝什麼東西呢?
What would he try to hang on that part of the wall?
站在這 我能看到二樓和樓下 暢通無阻
Well,from here, I have an unobstructed view of the second floor and down the stairs.
站在這堣]是 能看到整個入口處
It's the same thing down here. You can see the entire entrance.
是攝像頭 他裝了攝像頭
Cameras. He put up cameras.
我們認為這就是 他監視受害者的方法
We think this is what he's using to spy on his victims.
攝像頭體積小 價格低 容易隱藏 可以藏在相框 書 植物的後面
They're small,they're cheap, and they're easily hidden, behind photos,books,or plants.
錄下的片段可以傳輸到任何地方
The footage they record can then be transmitted anywhere.
你自己選的網站 甚至是手機上
Website of your choice, even your cell phone.
他還可以切換各個攝像頭 看到房子堛漱@切
And he can toggle between cameras to see everything that's happening in the house.
你們發現房子五個不同的位置 都有這些?
And you found 5 of these at different points in the house?
樓上 樓下 臥室 衛生間也有
Upstairs,downstairs, bedroom,even the bath.
他可以耍個花招進門 但沒時間裝五個
A ruse gets him in the door, but it doesn't buy him enough time to put up 5 of these.
對 所以我們認為 他會裝第一個面向前門
Right. That's why we think he starts with one camera facing the front door.
他就知道什麼時候進來是安全的
That tells him when it's safe to enter the house,
知道她什麼時候回家離家 遛狗人 什麼時候來 房子安保密碼是什麼
when she comes and goes, when the dog-walker comes, and what the combination to the house is.
這符合他的作案手法 他熟知受害人所有的社交細節
It fits his M.O. It he learned their every detail on social networks,
他會對這種監視上癮
he will be just as obsessive in his surveillance.
而一旦他瞭解了所有日程 他只需選好時間就行了
And once he learns their routine,all he has to do is pick the lock,
安裝好其他攝像頭 然後 他就對受害人的生活瞭如指掌了
put up the rest of the cameras, and boom,he got their whole life at his fingertips.
他怎麼處理那些錄像呢? 存著?
What does he do with the video? Maybe he keeps them?
如果他是窺淫狂的話就會
If he's a voyeur,yes.
啊 可窺淫狂一般不會有暴力行為
Ah,voyeurs are rarely violent.
他們興奮是因為目標人 不知道自己正在被監視
Their excitement comes from spying without the object knowing they're being watched.
罪犯綁架了受害人 也就去除了 發洩性慾的途徑 Reid說得對
And by abducting his victims, he's removing the outlet of his sexual release. Reid is right.
那這些攝像頭一定別有用意
So he must have some other agenda with these cameras.
也許他還和別人分享這些錄像
He might be sharing the footage with other people.
我們得讓Garcia查下 非法監視錄像的網站
We need to have garcia dig into surveillance in illegal video websites.
- 我要帶走這個 - 為什麼?
- I'm going to take this with us. - Why?
我們一開始側寫受害人之間 沒有面部相似點
We originally profiled there wasn't any facial similarity between the victims,
但我現在不是很確定了
but I'm not so sure that's true.
我想比對Dorris和其他受害人的照片
I want to compare dorris' picture with the other victims.
不明犯拍的這些錄像
These videos the unsub took,
有點像他傳到網上的一個 也許能幫我逮住他
it looks like one of them he posted online, which may help me nab it.
如果他放到了網上 你能直接追蹤回到他電腦嗎?
If he puts it on the web, can't you track that back directly to his computer?
正常來說可以
Normally,yes.
正常來說我能在17秒內 追蹤到他正在上的網絡
Normally, in like in 17 seconds I can get you the network he's using,
拿到他調製解調器的地址 然後突然之間 這世界就木有壞人了
get a physical address of his modem, and presto change-o, no more bad guy,
可是這個不明犯是個 恐怖的電腦發燒友
but this unsub is a creepy computer aficionado.
你們知道什麼是代理服務器嗎?
Do you guys know what a proxy server is?
是網絡中轉站
It's an internet relay.
正確 小孩子就用這玩意 避開被和諧的網站
Precisely. Kids use them to get around blocked sites.
一般來說一個代理服務器就足夠了 可這傢伙搞了幾十個
Now,usually one proxy is plenty, but this piece of work is using dozens of proxy servers.
中國 朝鮮 俄國 南非 都有他的信號...
He's bounced his signal off of china,north korea, russia,south africa...
Garcia 你能追蹤回到博伊西嗎?
Garcia,can you trace him back to boise?
當然能了 正在弄
Of course I can, and that's what I'm doing?
雖然很不幸地我需要點時間
Time is the unfortunate ingredient I need,though.
有了
This just in.
有一個存檔的代理服務器有信號了
Looks like one of the proxy servers archived
好像是Dorris Archer失蹤那晚的
what he was streaming on the night of dorris archer's disappearance.
- 我們能看到嗎? - 這就傳過去
- Can we see it? - Pulling it up now.
Prentiss和Morgan說得對 他對這房子瞭如指掌
Well,prentiss and morgan were right. He knows the house.
狗也認識他
And the dog knows him.
哦 拜託別傷害狗狗
Oh,please don't hurt that doggie.
要去過多少次才能這麼熟? 十幾次?
How many trips inside the house would that take? A dozen?
看到沒?
See that?
他身上裝著攝像頭 這是他的視角
The camera's attached to him. It's his point of view.
這樣他就能一次又一次地 重新體驗這一切了
So he can relive it over and over again.
有沒有人能告訴我結束了?
Ok,can someone tell me when this is over?
- 拜託 - 還沒
- Please. - Not yet.
他對她很溫柔 比起她活著 屍體對他來說更重要
He's tender to her. She means more to him as a corpse than as a living person.
Garcia 找到不明犯使用的網絡
Garcia,we need to find the unsub's network.
即使是大致區域 也能幫助我們縮小 地域範圍
Even if it's a rough area,it'll help narrow the geographic profile.
是 長官 我也正想找到他
Yeah. Sir,that's totally what I'm trying to figure out.
還有件事您需要知道
Uh,there is something else kind of huge you need to know about.
您看到這些代碼了嗎?
Do you see this line of code there?
看到了 怎麼了?
Yeah,what about them?
這能讓使用者管理網絡  也就是不明嫌犯 建立起一個聊天室
It allows the user admin, and in this case,the unsub, to set up a chat room.
人們能在謀殺案的當晚在線觀看
People were watching this on the night of the murder.
我們本來以為他是在事後上傳的 其實不是
We thought he was posting these after the fact. He's not.
他想讓別人和他一起感受這一切
He wants people to experience it with him.
他需要觀眾
He wants an audience.
他還有粉絲
He has fans.
能在這堸惜U嗎?
Can you freeze that?
他在向攝像頭致意
He's acknowledging the camera.
向粉絲脫帽致意 他知道他們在看
Tip of the hat to his fans. He knows they're watching.
典型的自戀行為
Classic narcissistic behavior.
他正在為觀眾表演
He's performing for his audience.
我們已經知道作案手法了 問題是如何實施
We know the M.O. The question is how.
什麼工作能讓他進入受害人家堜O?
What kind of job gives him access to the victims' houses?
一定和網絡有關 電訊的人可以幫你接網
It has to be network and I.T.S, the guy you let in to hook up your internet.
讓他進到房間 坐在電腦前
Gets him in their house and on their computers.
我仔細查過所有受害人的 網絡服務提供商
I went through all the women's internet service providers with a fine-tooth comb.
都是不同的公司 推銷員也不一樣
They all used different companies and no overlap with sales reps.
現場技術支持人員呢?
What about onsite tech support?
哦 都是清白的
Oh,well,clean as a whistle.
他們都有不在場證明 而且沒有犯罪記錄
They all had alibis with no criminal records.
我不明白他為什麼要在殺死那些人後 帶走她們的屍體
What I don't understand is, why does he take the bodies with him after they're dead?
把活著的受害者帶走 還解釋得通 但他已經完成任務了
Yeah,it'd be one thing if he took them while they were still alive, but he's accomplished his task.
他殺了那些人 完成了自己的演出
He murders them and he completes the performance.
那為什麼要冒險把屍體放到車上呢
So why take the risk of carrying a corpse to your car?
他一定還對屍體做了什麼舉動 或者想留下個性簽名 我們沒注意到
Well,there must be some postmortem behavior or signature or something we're not seeing.
我們仔細想想
Well,think about that for a second.
他讓很多人旁觀他的謀殺過程
He's sharing this murder with a crowd of onlookers.
而當他獨處的時候 他會怎樣對待這些屍體
What could he be doing to these bodies just for himself?
嘿 Garcia有信息給我們 說吧 姑娘
Hey,guys. Garcia's got something for us. Go ahead,baby girl.
好的 夥計們 我找到了一些東西 不過首先是壞消息
Ok,friends, I have some good news, but first,here is the thing that sucks.
我追蹤到不明嫌犯在博伊西使用的網絡 那是受害人自己的無線地址
I located the network the unsub is using in boise, and it is the victims' own wireless.
他在謀殺前 就侵入那些電腦了嗎?
So does he hack in before he starts with the murders?
黑進那些電腦太費時間了
Hacking is obscenely time-consuming.
你們看我黑電腦很容易 因為我是天才 可他不是
I just make it look easy because i'm a genius. But he's not me.
所以我猜 他在謀殺前 就埋伏進了她們的網絡
So my guess is that he's got to lurk around their network
至少得潛伏了好幾天到一周吧
for at least a couple of days to a week before he kills them.
他這麼干還挺聰明的
That's pretty brilliant on his part.
對 他知道如果我們追蹤他的網絡行蹤 只能查回到謀殺地點
Yeah,he knows when we follow his online paper trail that it'll lead us right back to the murder site.
好消息是什麼
What's the good news?
黑客們都有自己獨特的入侵技巧
Hackers are very loyal to their spoofing techniques,
如果覺得自己行蹤隱秘 便會重複使用同一路徑
and if they think no one's watching, they'll use the same roads over and over.
好 如果他再次借用俄羅斯 中國 朝鮮的服務器
Ok,so if he goes through russia, china,and north korea again...
我已經標記了那些服務器了 如果他再走同樣的路徑 我就能很快抓住他
I have flagged those servers, and if he uses them in the same order, I will catch him so fast.
只有他再次犯案 我們才能抓住他
That's only going to help us if he commits another murder.
- 是這樣 - 抱歉
- Yes,that's also true. - Excuse me.
Garcia 如果他再這麼做 你要花多久才能確定他的網絡
Garcia,if he does stream this again, how much time will you need to find the network?
哦 國際網很不穩定 我也不能確定 我...
Oh,uh,that's hard to guess with all the international pinging. I...
- 大概 - 呃 7分鐘吧
- Ballpark. - Uh,7 minutes?
不夠快 他作案只需要5分鐘
That's not fast enough. He's in and out of the house in 5.
哦天啊 那我就盡量縮短時間吧
Oh,god. I'm going to have to trim my time down,then.
Garcia 縮短時間
Garcia,get it done.
JJ 我們要召開一個記者招待會
Jj,we need to call a press conference.
既然我們知道他在殺害這些女性 就要把這個消息放出去
Now that we know how he's killing these women, we need to get it out there.
好的 我先篩選一下要召集的記者
Uh,all right, i'll,uh,prescreen the journalists I call on,
- 希望我們能控制住場面 - 很好
- hope we don't get anything out of left field. - Good.
我知道被害者之間的聯繫了
I know what connects the victims.
我仔細研究被害者的照片 我知道她們之間有某種聯繫
I was staring at pictures of the victims and I knew there was a pattern connecting them,
但不能確定是什麼 於是我使用了數學方法來分析
but I couldn't tell what it was until I broke it down mathematically.
為什麼我們都對名人的臉如此著迷
Why are we so drawn to celebrity faces?
因為他們的臉都存在對稱美
Because there's a symmetry to their beauty...
眼睛 鼻子 額頭到下巴的比例
The eyes,the ears,the ratio of the forehead to the chin.
這些比例越均衡 他們就越容易引人注意
The more balanced they are, the more appealing they are to our eye.
可這些女性並不是名人
These women aren't celebrities,though.
她們不是 可她們之間有共性
No,but there are similarities between them, and it wasn't
我掃瞄了這些照片 傳回匡提科分析之後 才完全明白了
until I scanned their pictures and got it to the guys at quantico that I had a full breakdown.
撇開眼睛的顏色 髮色 和膚色
All right,strip away eye color, hair color,and skin tone,
我們還能從幾何學上看出什麼
and what are we left with geometrically?
她們都長得有點不對稱
They're all slightly dystopic.
所有受害者的左眼都比右眼低一點
The left eye is slightly lower than the right eye on all the victims.
鼻子都很窄
All the noses are narrow.
額頭隆起的很相似
The forehead has the same ridge.
他可能都不知道 他究竟在她們身上看到了什麼
He might not even be aware that he sees it in them.
研究表明 我們選擇配偶時 都潛意識地
There have been studies that suggest that we pick our spouses subconsciously,
以我們看到的臉部對稱性作為基礎
based on a facial symmetry that we recognize.
所以不管有意無意 他發現了這一點 就要去殺死她們
So consciously or unconsciously, when he recognizes it, he has to destroy it.
也就是說 他只對身體有興趣 因為某些身體特徵與他有關聯
Which means he only has interest in the bodies as they relate back to him.
也許… 已經有所表現了
Maybe... They're a reflection.
記得在視頻最後他做了什麼嗎
Remember what he did at the end of the video?
他擦掉了眼淚
He wiped the tear away.
另一個他不該有的同情舉動
Another act of compassion he's not capable of.
他的自戀不會讓他這麼做
His narcissism prevents him from that.
在希臘神話中 那喀索斯太過自我迷戀
In the greek myth, narcissus was so self-absorbed
愛上了自己在水中的倒影
that he fell in love with his own reflection in the water.
沒錯 他尋找有同一張臉的女人
Exactly. He finds women with the same face,
掐死她們 再凝視她們死後的樣子
he strangles them,and then stares at them after they've died.
可他究竟看見了誰的形象
But whose image does he really see?
他自己
His own.
謝謝
Thank you.
我們認為使用網絡是理所當然的
Most of us take the internet for granted.
我們不會一直記得自己在 社交網站上分享和更新的文章
We forget about texts that we share or updates we put on social networks.
可是網絡把它們永久保存了下來
But the internet never forgets.
一旦上傳了 那些信息就永遠不會消失
Once it's out there, it's out there forever.
現在我們都知道那些 網上流傳的恐怖的殺人視頻
Now,we all know about the horrific deaths that get shown on the web.
謀殺記者
The murder of a journalist.
伊朗反對分子的投石事件
The stoning of an iranian dissident.
這些謀殺是不會為人所忘的
Those murders are immortal.
而這個不明嫌犯也渴求 被人同樣銘記
And this unsub craves that same immortality.
他在受害人身上看到自己的模樣 殺了她們 就好像在說
He recognizes his face on theirs and he kills them as a way of saying,
"我就長這個樣子"
"this is what I look like."
我們認為這也解釋了 他為什麼要帶走那些屍體
We think this also informs his compulsion to take the bodies with him.
他把屍體帶到第二犯罪現場 並在那保存起來
He takes them to a secondary location where we believe he preserves them,
所以每次看見那些屍體 他就能在它們身上看到自我
so that every time he looks at them, he sees his own ego reflected.
幸運的是 這也表示我們知道了他的長相
Fortunately for us, this means we have a good idea of what he looks like.
根據受害者的相貌 我們合成了一份大致的嫌犯畫像
Based on the shape of the victims' faces, we have a rough composite sketch.
這個不明嫌犯是電腦和家庭網絡的專家
This unsub is an expert with computers and home networks.
所以找找看電腦水平高超的人的犯罪記錄
So look into criminal records of men with extensive computer training.
我們知道 你們已經調查了 受害者電腦的通信設置
We know you've already looked into the victims' computer I.T.settings,
所以我們想擴大搜索範圍
so we'd like to expand the search.
調查電子商店 電腦經銷商 受害人就職公司的IT部門
Look into electronic stores, computer distributors,I.T.Departments where the women worked.
自戀的概念 在我們的文化中已經被濫用
We overuse the term narcissistic in our culture,
但這塈畯怍珨〞 是嚴格心理學定義
but we're going back to the psychological definition.
這個人的一生都是圍繞著 膨脹的自我而建立的
Every aspect of this man's life has been constructed around an inflated sense of self.
這樣的不明嫌犯容很易受到 自戀性損傷的傷害
Unsubs like this are particularly vulnerable to what's called narcissistic injury.
一旦他的自我價值受到攻擊或損傷 他就會抓狂
If his self-worth is attacked or damaged, he will lash out.
所以 如果你發現了這個不明嫌犯 不要公開挑戰他
So,if you find this unsub, do not challenge him publicly.
就說你只是想和他聊聊
Say you just want to talk him,
問他知不知道是哪個聰明絕頂的天才 跟蹤著這些女人
see if he knows anything about the brilliant mastermind who's stalking these women.
不管在什麼情況下都不要詆毀他
Under no circumstances should you denigrate him.
這雖然很不容易 但我們需要 誇讚他的戰績以示尊敬
As difficult as it is, we need to talk up his exploits as if we respected him.
這是我們正在尋找的男人的素描
This is a sketch of the man we're looking for.
白人男性 大約5英尺10
He is a white male, roughly 5'10".
對電腦和網絡技術非常熟悉
He's highly skilled with computers and networks.
我們建議大家監控好 上傳到社交網絡的個人資料
We encourage everyone to monitor the information they post about themselves on social networks.
不要寫下自己的詳細行程記錄
Do not document the details of your day.
不要上傳自己的 朋友的 或者家人的照片
Don't post pictures of yourself,friends,or family.
好了 可以問問題了 你?
All right,we'll take some questions. Yeah?
既然沒有目擊者 那FBI是怎麼得出這份素描的?
How did the fbi generate this sketch if there were no eyewitnesses?
是從我們修復的一段視頻中 得出的大概圖像
It's a approximation based on a video we recovered.
好了 你 你的問題是?
Ok,yeah, what's your question?
謠言說他與受害者的臉部特徵 有某種對稱性 能發表一下意見嗎?
Can you comment on the rumor he has some sort of facial symmetry with his victims?
他和受害者們長得像嗎?
Does he look like them?
到現在為止 博伊西警方有幾個不同的理論
Right now the boise police are pursuing several theories.
就是說你不否認
That's not a no.
為什麼他要把長得像他的女人當目標?
Why would he target women who look like him?
現在猜測他為什麼 怎麼樣 選擇受害者還言之過早
It's too soon to speculate on how or why he chooses his victims.
那人們要怎麼保護自己啊 整容嗎?
Well,what should people do to protect themselves,change their face?
不 注意更新自己的網絡安全 和謹慎處理自己上傳的東西
No,just update your online security and be vigilant about what you post.
好了 問題問完了 謝謝大家
All right,we're done with questions. Thank you.
Hotch 有人洩露了我們的側寫
Hotch. Somebody leaked our profile.
記者們在問關於臉部對稱性的問題
The press started asking questions about facial symmetry.
一定是你們當中的警員
It must have been one of your officers.
我的人之前是在看他們的手機 但只是慣性動作而已
Look,my guys were checking their cell phones, but that's just habit now.
我可以私下單獨的和媒體說一下 10點鐘新聞暫時可以不播出來 但...
All right,I can talk to the press independently, I can keep this off the 10:00 news,but...
我知道 剛剛是直播
I know. It went out live.
他沒看到的機會有多大?
Well,what are the chances he didn't see it?
情況不樂觀
Not good.
你這狡猾的神經病
Oh,your crafty little sicko.
長官 你打來得剛好 我剛琢磨出來...
Sir,it's fantastic you called. I just figured out...
你知道怎麼控制網絡了嗎?
How are you doing on pinning down the networks?
我剛剛正想告訴你
Ok,that's what I'm trying to tell you.
記得我跟你說過 他是怎麼通過 不同的服務器 來隱瞞自己信號的嗎?
Remember how I said he was spoofing his signal off different servers?
其中的某些 只不過是陷阱 用來消磨我的時間的
Well,it turns out some of those are a decoy meant to waste my time.
就是說 你能用更短的時間找到他?
So does that mean you can find him faster?
是的 是的 我能寫一個程序 篩選掉他的這些陷阱...
Totally. Totally. I can write a program that filters out the decoys...
- 噢 糟糕 - 是他嗎?
- Oh,crap. - Is that him?
是的 我要同時篩選這個
Yeah. Ok. It looks like I'm gonna have to filter this on the fly.
- 你能把視頻發給我們嗎? - 我想我能在烏克蘭境內攔截它
- Can you send us the feed? - I think I can intercept it in ukraine.
他在現場直播
He's going live.
看看他走路的方式 不像之前那樣不慌不忙 他被激怒了
Look at the way he's moving. He's not slow and deliberate. This guy's pissed.
我們能看出什麼? 有什麼明顯的標誌
All right,what do we see? Determining markers.
- 一層樓的別墅 - 哪都有可能
- A one-story cottage. - It could be anywhere.
有門牌號嗎?
Is there a number on the house?
- 沒有 他已經到門口了 - Garcia
- No,and he's already at the door. - Garcia.
他的代理服務器數量增加了一倍
He's using twice as many proxy servers.
等等 那下面的窗口 是個聊天室嗎?
Wait. This window here on the bottom... Is that the chat room?
- 她在這 - 他已經進屋了 同志們
- There she is. - He's in the house,guys.
他完全改變了他的作案手法 作案時間提早太多了
He's completely changed his M.O. It is way too early.
光線充足 發生什麼事了?
There's too much light. What happened?
有人在記者會上問錯問題了
Someone asked the wrong question at the press conference.
天啊 轉身啊 轉過來啊
Oh,my god,turn around. Just turn around.
或許她能擊退他
Maybe she can fend him off.
新的廚房用具 我們能從訂單上追查它們嗎?
New kitchen appliances. Can we track them through work orders?
- 查到的時候他早走了 - Garcia 給我們點什麼吧
- He'll be gone by then. - Garcia,give us something.
我已經追到國內了 快到愛達荷了 還需要一點時間
I'm stateside now. I'm almost to idaho.I just need more time.
- 你追不上的了 - 會的 我會的 我會的 我...
- You're not gonna make it. - Yes,I will. I will. I...
別管不明嫌犯了 你能追查在聊天室堛漱H嗎?
Forget the unsub. Can you run a trace on everybody in the chat room?
我不能兩個一起做 長官 讓我完成這個吧
I can't do both,sir. Let me do this.
Garcia 標記上正在看的人 這是命令
Garcia,tag the viewers. That's an order.
寶貝姑娘 沒事的
Baby girl,it's gonna be ok.
不 不 有事 我身邊死那麼多人已經夠糟糕的了
No,no,it's not. It's bad enough that there's been so much death around me,
但這個人 在我頭上動土 他真的很厲害 但太可怕了
but this guy is all up in my turf, and he's really good at what he does for really awful reasons.
所以你要把聊天室 那些變態觀眾都揪出來
That's why you're gonna find the perverts that watched it happen in that chat room,
我們會把他們掰倒 他們就會供出不明嫌犯
and we'll nail them to the wall and they're gonna give up the unsub.
不不 這樣還不夠 我要看著他受罪
No,no,that is not good enough. I want to watch him suffer.
我要看著他流血
I want to watch him bleed.
- 噢天吶 我嚇著自己了 - 很好啊 這是好事
- Oh,god,I just scared myself. - Good. That's a good thing.
因為我得到的教訓 就是你最不應該得罪的
Because if there's one thing i've learned the hard way is the last person you want to tick off
就是Penelope Garcia小姐
is miss penelope garcia.
- 你是在表揚我 是吧? - 是的
- That's a compliment, right? - Yes,it is.
相信我們會打敗這人的
We will beat this guy. Believe that.
- 我們查到什麼再給你打電話吧 - 好的
- Now,i'll call you when we've got something. - Ok.
她叫Allison Kittridge 29歲 這是她買的第一套房子
Her name was allison kittridge,29. This was her first house.
不明嫌犯加快了作案時間 升級了作案手法
All right,so this unsub accelerated his timetable and his M.O.
他加速是因為他生氣了
He was moving faster because he was angry.
是的 記者們說了些他不樂意聽到的話 所以他匆忙了事
Yeah. The press conference told him something about himself he didn't like, so he rushed.
意味著他犯了錯誤 那錯誤是什麼呢?
Which means he made a mistake. Now,what was it?
不是攝像頭 他把它們帶走了
Well,it wasn't the cameras. He remembered to take those with him.
不是屍體 他把她也帶走了
It wasn't the body. He took that with him,too.
嘿 Allison的無線接收器 Garcia有沒有發現不尋常的地方?
Hey,did,uh,garcia find anything unusual with allison's wireless?
沒 記錄上顯示的是一個基本的DSL裝置
No. Records show that it was a basic dsl installation.
- Prentiss 幫我搬開這桌子 - 好的
- Hey,prentiss.Help me move this table. - Yeah.
發現什麼了嗎?
What do you got?
你看到這堻o條線嗎?
You see this line right here?
是的?
Yeah.
網絡通過這條線接入室內
This is what brings the internet from the street into the house.
- 然後呢? - 這個不是DSL
- Ok. So? - This isn't dsl.
- 它不是? - 它是一條光纖線啊
- It's not? - It's a fiber-optic cable.
完全不一樣的連接
Completely different type of connection.
我們發現他犯的錯誤了
We just found his mistake.
如果屋堨豪荋N有網絡連接 他為什麼要帶上他自己的呢?
If there's already an internet connection in the house, why does he bring his own with him?
為了上傳速率嗎?
Is it the upload speed?
光纖可以讓他同步直播大量視頻
Fiber-optic allows him to stream large amounts of video.
同時開著聊天室
And maintain a chat room.
一次就有一大堆的電腦和他聯絡
That's dozens of computers connected to him at once.
為此 他需要很大的帶寬
He'd need a lot of bandwidth for something like that.
我們查了所有的網絡服務提供商 為什麼沒查到他?
We checked all the isps. Why didn't he turn up?
我老收到郵件 電話 甚至有人上門推銷 要我升級自己的網絡
I get mail,phone calls, people knock on my door all the time to see if I want to upgrade my internet.
是啊 我也是
Yeah,I get them,too.
他們會提出進屋演示 自己的聯接服務能比之前快多少
And they'll offer to come inside and demonstrate how much faster their connection is.
你認為他就是靠這幌子登堂入室的?
You think that's the ruse that gets him in the door?
這說得通啊 演示過程中 他有機會接近受害人的電腦
It makes sense. During his demonstration, he would have access to his victims' computers.
出門的時候 他要瓶水喝
On his way out, he asks for a glass of water,
支開主人 就有足夠時間 去放置第一個攝像頭
a distraction,something to buy enough time to plant that first camera.
我們得找出這光纖電纜是哪個公司的
We need to find out what company owns this cable.
Fordham探長已經在查了
Detective fordham's already hunting that down,
電纜上有ID號 所以應該不會要很長時間
and there's an I.D.Number on it,so it shouldn't take long.
JJ和Reid做下跟蹤吧
We'll have jj and reid follow up.
你倆去跟蹤當時聊天室堛漱H
I need you two to track down who was in the chat room.
Garcia掃瞄完了麼?
Garcia finished her sweep?
是的 大部分是國際的 三個是本地的
Yeah. Most were international. 3 were local.
我賭他們中有一個認識不明疑犯
I bet one of them knows the unsub.
FBI 我們有逮捕令
Fbi. We have a warrant.
有什麼可幫忙的麼?
Help you gentlemen?
- Austin Chapman? - 是的 是我
- Austin chapman? - Yeah,that's me.
FBI 關於你昨晚看的某段視頻 我們要跟你談談
Fbi. We need talk to you about a video you watched last night.
不好意思 什麼視頻?
I'm sorry. What video?
這是搜查令 我們有權搜查你名下所有電腦
This is a warrant for all the computers in your possession.
你因從犯謀殺被捕了
You're under arrest for accessory to murder.
從犯?
Accessory?
在線觀看謀殺 並且不作為 是重罪
Watching a murder happen online and doing nothing about it is a felony.
我不懂你在講什麼 什麼謀殺?
I don't know what you're talking about. What murder?
是的 這是我們的電纜
Yes,this is our cable.
Hightower夫人 我們看了你們的記錄
Mrs. Hightower,we went over your records,
4個受害人中 沒人使用你們的電纜
and it turns out that none of the 4 victims signed up with your service.
4個? 天啊 這些可憐的女人們
4? God,those poor women.
我們認為是你們的一個僱員 用你們的電纜作幌子進入房間
We think it's an employee using your cable as a ruse to get into the house.
- 你能想到有誰... - Mac Jones
- Can you think of any... - Mac jones.
他在我們的一部卡車上工作 我們把光纖和普通電話線捆綁接入
Uh,he worked on one of our trucks as we laid the fiber in with the regular phone line.
你確定是他麼?
And you're certain that it's him?
我們抓到他囤積電纜 他說這是為了一個家庭項目
We caught him hoarding it. He said it was for a home project.
直到我們接到投訴電話 說他拿著這些 挨家挨戶推銷免費光纖接入
Until we got angry phone calls that he was going door to door offering free fiber-optic installation.
- 我們當時就炒了他 - 我們需要他的資料
- We fired him on the spot. - We need his information.
沒問題
Absolutely.
女士們先生們 會見一下Mac Jones
Ladies and gentlemen, meet mac jones.
這不是我們從電話公司得到的身份證號
That isn't the I.D. We got from the phone company.
那是因為去年 Jones先生的身份證明被偷了
That's because last year mr. Jones had his identity stolen.
不明疑犯拿著他的證件和信用卡 用了2個星期 然後就不用了
The unsub took his license and his credit card, used them for 2 weeks, and then moved on.
我不能確定 不明疑犯正在冒充誰
Now,I can't tell you who the unsub is pretending to be now,
但是 一張圖片勝過萬千數據 我能告訴你們他是誰
but since a picture's worth a thousand databases, I can tell you who he was.
Robert Johnson 3進宮 由於擁有酷刑視頻被拘捕
Robert johnson,3-time loser, arrested for possession of torture videos.
在過渡教習所待了一段時間 就不見了
Spent some time in a halfway house before he disappeared.
我找到了他的一個博客 有這麼一句話...
I found a blog of his online. Here's a quote...
"下一次 你就阻止不了我了"
"next time you won't be able to stop me."
他又自戀了
That's his narcissism again.
對於被捕一事 他很憤怒 便把自己改造成了一個殺手
Furious that he got caught and he remakes himself as a killer.
這讓他得以釋放本來就有的衝動
It allows him to free the impulses that were always there.
Garcia 他盜竊身份 有什麼模式嗎?
Garcia,is there a pattern to the identities that he steals?
沒有 他非常小心
No. He's really disciplined about it.
一個身份一旦被用過 絕不會再用第二次
Once he burns through an identity, he never uses the same one again.
知道嗎? 有些嫌疑犯 完全無跡可尋
You know how I describe some suspects as being off the grid?
這傢伙完全相反 到處都是他的蹤跡
This guy is totally the opposite. He's all over the grid.
一切行蹤在他掌控之下
He's manipulating the grid.
而且他從不在同一地點待很久
And he never stays in one place for very long.
那我們現在要怎麼找到他?
So how do we find out who he is now?
我覺得找不到 這個叫 Robert Johnson的人是浮雲啊
I don't think we're going to. The man known as robert johnson is in the wind.
如果他和他的名字一樣多變 那就無需記住真名
If he's this flexible with his name,his real name,forget it.
- 但另有辦法找到他 - 是什麼?
- But there's another way we can find him. - Which is?
他的網名 他的黑客頭銜
His online name, his hacker handle.
這才是他在意的名字
That's the name that matters to him.
等等 他不會有成堆的網名嗎?
Wait. Wouldn't he have hundreds of those,too?
應該是 但還記得我說過 黑客很忠誠麼?
Most definitely. But remember how I said hackers are loyal?
他們偏好使用某幾個名字
They stick to certain names.
這樣才能向其他黑客證明自己的身份
That's how you identify yourself to other hackers.
FBI就是這麼逮到我的
That's how the fbi caught me.
所以如果我們找到這個黑客頭銜...
So if we find the handle...
我會找到不明嫌犯 我保證
I'll get you the unsub. I promise.
我希望我能幫你們 找到那個上傳視頻的傢伙
Look,I wish I could help you find the guy posting these videos,
但我從沒上過那個網站 哥們
but I never visited that website,man.
是啊
Right.
或許是有人黑進我的電腦怎麼的
Maybe somebody broke into my computer or something.
聽著 scott  我們認為是你
See,scott,we think it was you.
在你的硬盤媮晪鋮鴞n多有趣的視頻 更證明了我們的想法
And we found some pretty interesting movies in your hard drive to back up our theory.
"白人女孩不能上" 很好誒
"white girls can't hump." That's nice.
"辛德勒的拳頭"
"schindler's fist."
看 這個 這個可引人注意啊
See,this one right here,this is the one that got my attention.
"Sandy的性愛覺醒"
"the erotic awakenings of sandy."
視頻堥漱k孩才幾歲? 12歲?
How old was the girl in that video? What was she,12?
我 我可以解釋...
I... I can explain...
閉嘴!
Shut up!
我就覺得這個蹊蹺
This is what's weird to me.
你的大部分文件都是加密的 唯獨除了少女毛片
Most of your files were locked away, but not the child porn.
我們5分鐘就找到了
We found it in like 5 minutes.
沒有密碼保護 什麼都沒有
It wasn't password protected or anything.
像你這麼精通電腦的人 怎麼會做這麼蠢的事兒?
How does someone who's supposed to be so smart with computers do something so dumb?
我們能做個交易麼?
Can we cut a deal?
你告訴我想知道的東西 然後才有交易可談
You tell me what I want to know and the maybe we'll talk deal.
在他接受你進入俱樂部之前...
Before this guy accepts you into the club...
他給你一些非法的東西 孩子 酷刑
He gives you the illegal stuff. Kids. Torture.
他要知道你和他一樣願意冒險
He has to know that you're risking as much as he is.
確保他死你亡
Mutually assured destruction.
你把他供出來 他把你也拖下水
You rat him out, he takes you with him.
是的
Yes.
- 他叫什麼? - 我不知道 從沒見過面
- What's his name? - I don't know. We never met.
別想耍我 小屁孩兒
Don't you try and play me,kid.
他的網名
His online name.
偷窺者89
Watcher 89.
還有別的名字麼?
Were there any other names?
我沒找到過
Not that I could find.
我不會為毛片註冊 除非我知道是誰在操控
I don't like signing up for porn unless I know who's running it.
Prentiss女士
Mrs. Prentiss.
- Prentiss探員 - 還有件事
- Agent prentiss. - There's something else you should know.
他發了個消息 說今晚會是最美好的
He sent out a message. He said tonight would be the best one yet.
他今天晚上要發動襲擊?
He's attacking tonight?
當然 他知道你們盯上他了
Of course. He knows you're watching him.
他要來一場特別精彩的表演
He has to put on an extra-good show.
說點有意思的 Chapman先生 我們詢問了另外兩個人
What's interesting, mr. Chapman, the two other men we talked to,
他們的硬盤 都有某種形式的抵押籌碼
they had a form of collateral on their hard drive.
什麼抵押籌碼?
- I'm sorry. - Collateral?
赤裸的性愛錄像 違法的 充滿暴力
Hard-core pornography. Illegal. Rough.
我根本不看那東西
I would never look at something like that.
我的電腦都在你們那兒 你們一定檢查過了
You have all my computers. You must have searched them.
是的 我們什麼都沒發現
Yes. And we found nothing.
- 那 我能走了嗎? - 不行
- So,can I go? - No.
我得多問一句
You see,there's still that nagging question as to
你昨天晚上為什麼登錄那個聊天室
why you were logged on to that chat room last night.
Rossi探員 你瞧 留我在這兒純屬浪費時間
Look... Agent rossi, i'm at a loss here.
首先 計算機方面我一竅不通
First of all,I'm all thumbs when it comes to computers.
也沒準是高手 知道怎麼消滅蹤跡
Or you're very good with them and know how to cover your tracks.
再說 昨天晚上我的孫子們來過夜
Second of all, my grandkids were at the house last night for a sleepover.
他們8點半就上床睡覺了
They were in bed by 8:30.
我們都累跨了 我和我媳婦9點就睡了
We were so exhausted,my wife and I were asleep by 9:00.
拜託! 你去問問她 她也會這麼說的
Please! Ask her. She'll say the same thing.
我昨天晚上連郵箱都沒打開
I don't think I even checked my email last night.
認識這個人嗎?
Do you know this man?
認識 他前一陣來過我店
Yes. He came into my store a while back.
為什麼?
Why?
他說他喜歡我的網站
Uh,he said he liked my website.
那是我兒子幫我設計的
Which my son designed for me,by the way.
我們聊起了家電 他買了幾樣東西就走了
We chatted about appliances, he bought a few items and left.
- 他說他叫什麼了嗎? - 不知道 我們聊了差不多5分鐘
- Did he have a name? - No idea. We talked for 5 minutes.
我馬上回來
I'll be right back.
你相信他嗎?
Do you believe him?
他不符合對其他窺淫狂的側寫
I believe he doesn't fit the profile of the other voyeurs.
他們都精通電腦
They're good with computers.
都做過黑客
They have hacking experience.
Garcia檢查了網站 說是很粗糙
Garcia checked out the website. She said it's crude.
連訂單都下不了
You can't even order anything from it.
也許他說的對 不明嫌犯擺佈他是另有所圖
Maybe he's right. Maybe the unsub manipulated him for something else,
把他的網站作為自己偽裝的一部分
used his network as part of his spoofing.
- Garcia 請講 - 偷窺者89 我找到他了
- Go ahead,garcia. - Watcher 89... I got him.
他有自己的網絡?
Does he have his own network?
他不需要 他可以附著在全市範圍內的網絡
He doesn't need one. He's got a whole city to leech off of.
他今天晚上還要行動
He's doing this again tonight.
你能列出他最近盜取的賬號嗎?
Can you send me a list of networks he's hacked recently?
這些都是潛在的受害者
Those are the potential victims.
- 有20個 - 很好 除去男性和有家室的
- I got 20 hits. - All right. Filter out men and families.
- 他只對單身女性下手 - 還有8個
- He only kills single women. - 8 left.
Garcia 有照片嗎?
Garcia,do you have any pictures?
傳過去了
Coming your way.
- 她 就是她 - Lucy Masters 你確定嗎?
- Her. She's the one. - Lucy masters. You sure?
只有她的臉部對稱度能吸引他
She's the only one with facial symmetry that would appeal to him.
- Lucy Masters? - FBI! 我們進來了
- Lucy masters? - This is the fbi! We're coming in.
- 沒人! - 沒人!
- Clear! - Clear!
她人不在 但是車在
She's not here, but her car is.
它自己開的
It just went on by itself.
那是Lucy Masters
That's lucy masters.
他在給我們錄像
He's recording us.
歡迎欣賞我的節目
Welcome to the show.
Garcia 不明嫌犯正要退出 Lucy Masters的網路
Garcia,the unsub is working off lucy masters' network.
你能查出視頻要傳到哪兒嗎?
Can you tell where the video's being transmitted to?
沒辦法查 他不是用偷窺者89登錄的
I can't tell. He's not logged in as watcher 89.
他沒有用常用的代理服務器
He's not using any of the regular proxy servers.
多虧我眼明 才知道哪個是他
If I didn't know any better,I wouldn't know that this was him.
我靠! 他給代理服務器加密了
Damn it! He's encrypted his connection to the proxies.
我也無能為力了
There's nothing I can do to help you find him.
- 我們能看出什麼? - 金屬牆面
- What do we see? - Metal walls.
肯定是他處理受害人的另一個地點
It must be the secondary location where he takes the victims.
等一下 Garcia 能把她後面的牆面放大嗎?
Wait a minute. Garcia,can you magnify the wall behind her?
這個我能行
Yeah,I can do that.
牆上那是霜嗎?
Is that frost on the wall?
- 是個冷藏室 - 我知道他從哪兒找來的了
- It's a walk-in freezer. - And I know where he got it.
- 我們沒抓錯你啊 Austin - 什麼?
- We didn't catch you by mistake,did we,austin? - Excuse me?
你說不明嫌犯喜歡你的網站設計
You said the unsub liked your website, how it was designed.
但其實是你的工作
But it was your work.
你能幫他修理和修復的東西
What you can repair, what you can restore for him.
你給他提供了一個藏屍體的地方
You gave him a place to hide the bodies.
沒這回事 你去問我媳婦
That's not true. Talk to my wife.
我每天晚上6點到家
I'm home by 6:00 every night...
窺淫狂須知第一條
That's the first thing voyeurs learn.
如何毀滅蹤跡
How to cover their tracks.
如何在9點到5點之間跟蹤
How to stalk between the hours of 9:00 to 5:00.
所以你電腦上沒有小黃片
That's why there was no porn on your computer.
你有更刺激的東西
You had something better.
這是犯罪啊!
This is a crime!
你說的那些我根本不會做
I would never do what you're describing.
就算你不相信我 我媳婦也明白啊
And even if you don't believe me,my wife knows.
我兒子 我孫子
My kids,my grandkids.
我討厭電腦 我根本就不知道怎麼用
I hate computers. I don't even know how they work.
那我給你上第一課
Well,then let me give you your first lesson.
什麼東西一旦掛到網上 就永遠抹不掉了
When something goes out on the internet,it's out there forever.
現在你要進監獄了
Now,you're going to jail.
這是板上釘釘的
That's a foregone conclusion.
除非你跟我合作
But,unless you cooperate with me,
不然我會想方設法讓你孫子下次 再google你的時候
I will do everything I can to make sure that the next time your grandkids google you,
能發現他們的爺爺到底有多變態
they will find out what kind of a monster grandpa really is.
現在我再問一遍
Now,I will ask you once...
那個冷藏室在哪兒?
Where is the freezer?
Hudson街 1823號 知道了 我們這就過去
1823 hudson. I got it. We're on our way.
Garcia 信號已經直播了3分鐘
Garcia,it's been 3 minutes sinc the signal went up live.
Lucy可能沒多少時間了
Lucy might not have that much time left.
我能幫你爭取一點 現在我有他的實際地址
I can buy you some.Now that i've got his physical address,
我使出全力了
I got my business all up in his.
不 不 今天你沒戲
No,no,not today.
不! 不!
No! No!
現在你網絡癱瘓 一整天都白費了 是不是呀 小變態?
Now,when your internet goes down, it ruins your whole day, doesn't it,psycho?
不!
No!
- 放開她! 把手拿開! - 不!
- Get off her! Let her go! Get your hands off! - No!
- 放開她! - 不!
- Let her go! - No!
- Lucy - 叫醫護人員過來!
- Lucy. - Get the paramedics in here!
好了 好了 沒事了
Ok. Ok. It's over. It's ok.
快走
Go,go,go,go.
Morgan
Morgan.
那是Dorris Archer
It's dorris archer...
還有Allison Kittridge
And allison kittridge.
你為粉絲殺人
You killed these women for your fans,
但這些 都是給自己留著的吧 你個缺德大混蛋
but this is where you kept them for yourself,isn't it, you sick son of a bitch.
看著她們你什麼感想?
What do you see when you look at them?
我做的事你永遠也不會懂
You'll never understand what I did.
但是我的追隨者們明白
But out there, my followers... They understand.
很遺憾 監獄堥S有無線
Well,too bad there's no wireless in prison.
把他帶出去!
Get him out of here!
"互聯網是第一個由人類創造 而人類又無法理解的事物
"the internet is the first thing that humanity has built that humanity doesn't understand,
是迄今為止 最大規模的無政府狀態的實驗"
the largest experiment in anarchy that we have ever had."
Eric Schmidt (Google首席執行官)
Eric schmidt.
告訴你一聲
Just for the record...
這不是我幹的
I didn't do this.
本地商人 因協助網絡謀殺犯被捕
犯罪心理 第五季 第22集 網絡永恆
== 結束 ==
Criminal Minds Season05 Episode22 The Internet Is Forever